

Madhya Pradesh, India

**\( +91 9131810998** 

☑ rai.sanidhya2010@gmail.com

github.com/sani-Alpha

in linkedin.com/in/sanidhya-rai-b5318a135/

# Summary

Currently a student at Vellore Institute Of Technology. A technology enthusiast with keen interest in software development. Enabled myself to be an efficient reader and writer who can also be quick witted to deal with sudden tasks. A fun loving person who is also prompt at work and comes with leadership and managerial skills. Looking out for work experience as an intern or full time to hone my skills and knowledge so that I can contribute towards the betterment of society.

## Work experience

#### Intern as Developer

05/2019 - Present

Adhoc Networks Infotech Private Limited, Jaipur

Working as a intern developer for a year

**Intern/Trainee** 05/2019 - 06/2019

Adhoc Networks Infotech Private Limited, Jaipur

Working as a trainee for course in Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence.

#### Intern as Content Writer

12/2018 - 03/2019

Fantasktic, Inc

Have been writing and proof-reading content on topics like SEO, Social Media Marketing, Pay Per Click, User Experience and Product Management.

#### Education

#### **B.** Tech in Computer Science

08/2017 - Present

Vellore Institute of Technology, Bhopal

Pursuing my graduation degree: in Engineering in B. Tech Computer Science

**Class 12th (ISC)** 04/2015 - 03/2017

The Sanskaar Valley School, Bhopal

I completed my Higher Secondary Education with a percentage of 82% and Subject Proficiency in Computer Science (All India Top Scorer)

Class 10th (ICSE) 02/2014 - 03/2015

The Sanskaar Valley School, Bhopal

I completed my Secondary Education with a percentage of 92.8% and Subject Proficiency in Computer Science (98 percentile)

**Chatbot - Baymax** 06/2019 - 07/2019

### Adhoc Networks Infotech Private Limited, Jaipur

An Al powered chatbot that works on sentimental analysis. It predicts the emotional state of the user from the text and plays songs accordingly to cheer up the person.

# 8 Bit Mini-Computer

02/2019 - Present

Vellore Institute of Technology, Bhopal

Along with my team, we are designing a 8-bit Mini Computer capable of performing smaller tasks and calculations. We are trying to implement a voice control module to basically execute voice commands.

**Tic-Tac-Toe** 03/2018 - 05/2018

## Vellore Institute of Technology, Bhopal

Basically a game of Tic-Tac-Toe, based on python's pygame library. Comes with an UI and is playable against computer as well as player

**Sudoku Solver** 02/2019 - 04/2019

## Vellore Institute of Technology, Bhopal

Sudoku is a well known puzzle which comes with a number of variants. This project implements a CPU that solves the sudoku. Pass the predefined set of conditions and run.

## Skills

Java (Programming Language)			
Leadership			
Python (Programming Language)			
Machine Learning			
Web Development			
Content Writer			
C++ (Programming Language)			
C (Programming Language)			

	Red Hat Linux			
	Public Speaking			
	Teamwork			
	English (Proficiency)			
	Amazon EC2			
Cei	rtificates			
	Data Science Specialisation in Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Neural Networks and Al	06/2019		
	Adhoc Networks Infotech Private Limited, Jaipur			
	Red Hat Certified System Administrator in Red Hat	06/2019		
	Adhoc Netwroks Infotech Private Limiited, Jaipur			
	Certified Microsoft Innovative Educator Microsoft	2015		
	Microsoft Powerpoint 16 Specialist Microsoft	2015		
Other Achievements and Skills				
	<b>Under 19 Basketball State Tournament</b> SGFI	2016		
	Under 19 Basketball Open National Tournament IPSC (Indian Public School Conferenece)	2015		
	Under 19 Swimming State Competition SGFI	2015		
	Silver Badge Earned  IAYP (International Award for Young People)	2016		

String Art